<Document>
  [italic]While in-game, you're expected to follow the following rules.
  I tried my best to keep them short and simple so you'll actually read/follow them[/italic] 

  [bold]1) Remain In-Character[/bold]
  While in game, everything you see is canon and in-character. 
  Avoid using /looc chat, save it for questions you can't ask IC
  Don't ignore bugs, admin actions, or even rulebreaks. Handle it all ICly using in-game lore.

  [bold]2) No Metagaming[/bold]
  Metagaming is your character using knowledge you learned unconscious, on another character, or via OOC means.
  You are allowed to talk about the current round in chat, you just cannot use any info you learned. 
  Unintentional metagaming is always a risk, so be careful about sharing info that could influence other's choices (such as metacoms).

  [bold]3) No Powergaming[/bold]
  Powergaming, aka godmodding, is behaving unrealistically either via game mechanics or unreasonable /me posts.
  Don't min-max traits, don't abuse glitches, don't be a Mary Sue, a murderhobo (RDM), and don't throw your life away (Fear RP).
  This is HRP; you will be called out for eating shit off the floor, not RPing out severe pain, being lewd in public, or not caring about others dying. 

  [bold]4) Accept Consequences[/bold]
  What separates HRP from MRP is continuity and consequence. There are no retcons unless admins approve it. 
  Criminal actions may result in getting your character jailed or even executed (permanently)
  Thus avoiding that punishment with new-lifing a similar character is an example of what is forbidden. 

  [bold]5) Forbidden Concepts[/bold]
  I try to be loose on this to allow for creative freedom, but I have to put a few rules down.
  You are not allowed to RP the following: LGBTphobia (In the year 2525, we've moved passed this), Pedophilia, Necrophilia, 
  Or anything that goes against player's personal consent info.
  You are also not allowed to name your characters after popular figures (both real and fake), and your names have to be realistic to your species.
</Document>